import type { ShareModalTextType } from '@/types/textTypes';
import type { LangStringType } from '@/types/common';

export const shareModalTexts: LangStringType<ShareModalTextType> = {
  ko: {
    shareModalTitle: '공유하기',
    shareModalClose: '닫기',
    twitter: '트위터',
    urlShare: 'URL 복사',
    otherAppShare: '다른 앱으로 공유',
    urlCopied: 'URL이 복사되었습니다',
    check: '확인',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: '',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: '현재 순위는⁉',
      title1: '순위는⁉',
      title2: '순위는⁉',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1위',
      second: '2위',
      voteDiffFront: '단',
      voteDiffBack: '표 차이',
      current: '현재',
      place: '위',
      lessThan: '',
      moreThan: '',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '와(과)',
      middlePageFront: '#팬플러스 투표 참여하고\n최애만을 위한 특별한 광고 선물하자 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: '현재 1위 : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: '지금 바로 #팬플러스 에서',
      endBack: '에게 투표하세요 ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻실시간 순위 확인하러 가기🔻',
    },
  },
  en: {
    shareModalTitle: 'Share',
    shareModalClose: 'Close',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: 'Copy URL',
    otherAppShare: 'Share to other apps',
    urlCopied: 'URL copied',
    check: 'Check',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: 'as of',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: 'Current Ranking',
      title1: 'Current Ranking',
      title2: 'Current Ranking',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1st',
      second: '2nd',
      voteDiffFront: 'Winning by',
      voteDiffBack: 'votes',
      current: 'is currently',
      place: '. place',
      lessThan: 'less than',
      moreThan: 'more than',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: 'Participate in #FanPlus vote\nand give your bias AD rewards! 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: 'Currently winning : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: 'Vote',
      endBack: 'on #FanPlus right now! ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻Check the current ranking🔻',
    },
  },
  es: {
    shareModalTitle: 'Compartir',
    shareModalClose: 'Cerrar',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: 'Copiar URL',
    otherAppShare: 'Compartir con otras aplicaciones',
    urlCopied: 'URL copiado',
    check: 'Confirmar',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: 'as of',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: 'Current Ranking',
      title1: 'Current Ranking',
      title2: 'Current Ranking',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1st',
      second: '2nd',
      voteDiffFront: 'Winning by',
      voteDiffBack: 'votes',
      current: 'is currently',
      place: '. place',
      lessThan: 'less than',
      moreThan: 'more than',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: 'Participate in #FanPlus vote\nand give your bias AD rewards! 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: 'Currently winning : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: 'Vote',
      endBack: 'on #FanPlus right now! ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻Check the current ranking🔻',
    },
  },
  in: {
    shareModalTitle: 'Bagi',
    shareModalClose: 'Tutup',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: 'Salin URL',
    otherAppShare: 'Bagikan ke aplikasi lain',
    urlCopied: 'URL disali',
    check: 'Memeriksa',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: 'as of',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: 'Current Ranking',
      title1: 'Current Ranking',
      title2: 'Current Ranking',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1st',
      second: '2nd',
      voteDiffFront: 'Winning by',
      voteDiffBack: 'votes',
      current: 'is currently',
      place: '. place',
      lessThan: 'less than',
      moreThan: 'more than',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: 'Participate in #FanPlus vote\nand give your bias AD rewards! 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: 'Currently winning : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: 'Vote',
      endBack: 'on #FanPlus right now! ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻Check the current ranking🔻',
    },
  },
  ja: {
    shareModalTitle: '共有',
    shareModalClose: '閉じる',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: 'URLをコピー',
    otherAppShare: '他のアプリで共有',
    urlCopied: 'URLがコピーされました',
    check: '確認',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: 'as of',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: 'Current Ranking',
      title1: 'Current Ranking',
      title2: 'Current Ranking',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1st',
      second: '2nd',
      voteDiffFront: 'Winning by',
      voteDiffBack: 'votes',
      current: 'is currently',
      place: '. place',
      lessThan: 'less than',
      moreThan: 'more than',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: 'Participate in #FanPlus vote\nand give your bias AD rewards! 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: 'Currently winning : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: 'Vote',
      endBack: 'on #FanPlus right now! ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻Check the current ranking🔻',
    },
  },
  vi: {
    shareModalTitle: 'Chia sẻ',
    shareModalClose: 'Đóng',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: 'Sao chép UR',
    otherAppShare: 'Chia sẻ với các ứng dụng khác',
    urlCopied: 'Đã sao chép URL',
    check: 'Xác nhận',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: 'as of',
        back: '',
      },
      title0: 'Current Ranking',
      title1: 'Current Ranking',
      title2: 'Current Ranking',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1st',
      second: '2nd',
      voteDiffFront: 'Winning by',
      voteDiffBack: 'votes',
      current: 'is currently',
      place: '. place',
      lessThan: 'less than',
      moreThan: 'more than',
      voteDiff: '',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: 'Participate in #FanPlus vote\nand give your bias AD rewards! 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: 'Currently winning : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: 'Vote',
      endBack: 'on #FanPlus right now! ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻Check the current ranking🔻',
    },
  },
  'zh-CN': {
    shareModalTitle: '分享',
    shareModalClose: '关闭',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: '复制URL',
    otherAppShare: '共享到其他应用',
    urlCopied: 'URL已复制',
    check: '确认',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: '',
        back: '基准',
      },
      title0: '现在排名⁉',
      title1: '排名是⁉',
      title2: '排名是⁉',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1位',
      second: '2位',
      voteDiffFront: '仅',
      voteDiffBack: '票差',
      current: '现在是第',
      place: '位',
      lessThan: '',
      moreThan: '',
      voteDiff: '与第',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: '参加 #FanPlus 投票\n给最爱的偶像送上特别的礼物 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: '现在第1位 : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: '现在即刻 #在FanPlus上给',
      endBack: '投票吧 ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻查看实时排名🔻',
    },
  },
  'zh-TW': {
    shareModalTitle: '分享',
    shareModalClose: '關閉',
    twitter: 'Twitter',
    urlShare: '複製URL',
    otherAppShare: '分享到其他應用',
    urlCopied: 'URL已復制',
    check: '確認',
    shareTitleText: {
      standard: {
        front: '',
        back: '基準',
      },
      title0: '現在排名⁉',
      title1: '排名是⁉',
      title2: '排名是⁉',
    },
    shareMiddleText: {
      first: '1位',
      second: '2位',
      voteDiffFront: '僅',
      voteDiffBack: '票差',
      current: '現在是第',
      place: '位',
      lessThan: '',
      moreThan: '',
      voteDiff: '與第',
      with: '',
      middlePageFront: '参加 #FanPlus 投票\n给最爱的偶像送上特别的礼物 🎁🎈',
      middlePageBack: '现在第1位 : ❓❔',
    },
    shareEndText: {
      endFront: '現在即刻 #在FanPlus上給',
      endBack: '投票吧 ✊🏻✊🏻',
      endPage: '🔻查看實時排名🔻',
    },
  },
};
